This room looks like it was on
the receiving end of a tornado!
I don't understand how this hole
could be perfectly spherical.
What is going on?
I'm not sure, but the destruction
spreads into the other room, too.
It's safe to say Avdol and the
others made contact with the enemy.
Here we go!
Break down this door, Jotaro!
We're going in! Roger.
Hurrah!
Amazement.
Let's go to the social media?
My vision is like a simple!
Suite of the connect with the mirror.
I will wake you up.
The arrow goes out to
the journey of the light!
Written,
Kukaku no last page ni So
no kobushi wo Dead ki Cameo
End of the world?
So no chino Kick
Hear!
Au River, Iggy.
Polnareff, the blood that stains my
body is Avdol's handiwork, not yours.
My plan was to eradicate you both
simultaneously, but due to Avdol's intervention,
your demise was postponed.
Anyone else would have instinctively
saved himself over risking
life and limb to come to the
aid of an oblivious comrade.
That alone makes him
responsible for my injuries.
He may have been able to injure me,
but it'll take far more than
that to send me to the grave.
Now I'll set my sights
on the other interlopers.
I'll kill them in the name of Lord Dio!
Damn it.
I told you not to use your stand, Iggy,
but you just had to show off, didn't you?
Stupid dog.
Why'd you have to do it? Hold the riff!
As far as Cool Ice was concerned,
Iggy was nothing more than a filthy
stray without resolve or pride.
But by its very nature, a stand
is a manifestation of the soul,
and Iggy's had acted of its own volition?
with something compelling
it from deep within.
His sand, its spirit is gone.
How could this have happened? Damn it!
All that's left is a lifeless husk.
The shell of death is in the air and another
life has been cut short far too soon.
Why am I the only one who survived?
You're too slow for
your own good, Cool Ice.
But you know something?
You're right.
I had some pretty selfless friends, huh?
I was supposed to look out for
Iggy, but instead he saved my ass.
Damn it.
How could this be happening?
I've only just begun to
realize what he meant to me.
This is how it always is.
I don't get it until after they're gone.
You were a miserable
little mutt from the start,
but despite that, you never failed
to find new ways to impress me.
You were a proud bastard who
lived life by your own rules,
and we were the ones who mistook
your self-respect as indifference.
I told you not to save me!
Dammit, Fleabag!
Why'd you have to be so stubborn?
I knew it.
I figured out what you are, Cool Ice.
I knew there was something
strange about you.
You're an immortal.
Dio somehow found a way to transform you.
What the hell is this?
What's happening to me?
Obviously, your precious master made
the changes without your knowledge.
He gave you his blood, didn't he?
Guess he left out the part about
you turning into a vampire.
You're just like Dio now.
A disgusting, soulless vampire.
You bastard!
Since you're only feeling it now, the change
must have started after I stabbed you.
Come on!
You made a vow to protect
your lord and master, right?
What are you waiting for bring it? Yeah?
Go on do your worst.
Hey, what's the hold up
cool ice? I'm waiting.
You're not going to defeat me
Now go to hell asshole
Oh, my God.
Ah, Avdol, wait!
Iggy!
Was...
Was that my imagination?
Or was it really?
I don't have time to sit and ponder.
All that matters now is making
it upstairs and finding Dio.
Morning can wait.
I can't fall apart after
everything they sacrificed.
Japan, 43 days had passed since Jojo and
the others began their journey to Egypt.
Rosa, stop the car.
Hit the brakes, I want to get out.
Madam Joestar,
I don't mean to overstep,
but it's now really the best
time to stop at a sober stand.
Well, of course, I haven't
been to Japan in a while.
I'd like to grab a quick bite
before visiting my little girl.
Hon, would you be a dear
and hold on to my turtle?
Please madam you mustn't
places such as these are
for common businessmen
ladies of your pedigree!
Should only dine at fine
restaurants i'm begging
you madam don't go in
there lighten up Roses!
It's so quaint i just have to record it.
Oh the local flavor is simply to die for!
Oh this'll be a good shot.
Mr.
Roses, judging by the
madam's cavalier attitude,
I take it you've not told
her about Holly's condition?
Hey, what's the holdup, Roses?
Get over here!
I'm right behind you, madam!
No, I haven't uttered a single word.
As far as she knows, her daughter is
battling a severe case of pneumonia.
I've worked for the Joestar
family for the past 30 years.
As for Miss Holly, I've known her since
she was a little girl in grade school.
Believe me, I know that I
have to tell her the truth,
but I just don't have the heart.
Even coming to Japan hasn't
given me the courage.
Holly doesn't have long.
If she's not saved, she'll likely
die within the next few days.
Would you prefer that I
told Madam Joestar, sir?
No, thank you.
But I've made my bed with the
falsehoods I've told the madam,
and now I have to lie in it.
I have to be the one to inform her.
Tell me,
are you absolutely sure
the curse afflicting
Miss Holly will be
lifted if Dio is killed?
I am.
Dio's demise will end this, trust me.
Holly's body is reacting to energy
from something known as a stand.
But only people with said stands
can observe the phenomenon.
Put simply, Dio's dark energy
is slowly destroying her.
But Madam cannot see the stands.
Instead, she'll have to bear witness to
her only daughter in the throes of death.
She must know the time
for secrets is over.
Yes.
Yes, you're right.
There you are, Roses!
What are you still doing out here?
Instead of sulking around,
come have some curry udon!
Hmm, please listen, madam, there is
something that I need to tell you.
Oh, I must get some footage of this delightful
little health drink vending machine.
Another good shot.
Would you like me to get you one, Roses?
Wait, madam Joestar,
you have to stop this.
Despite appearances, those aren't drinks.
Madam, please, you have to listen to me.
My, what is it?
Well, uh, it's about Miss Holly.
Oh!
Look at this Japanese
man's unique fashion sense!
Very nice!
Hi there, how are you?
Give me a big smile if you would! Huh?
What the hell are you doing, lady?
Who gave you permission
to videotape me, huh?
Please, madam, get in the car.
Nice to meet you.
Come back here, dammit!
We're not done!
I'll be taking that camera
from you before you leave!
Who do you think you are?
You're just a damn foreign hag!
You're looking to see some
blood today, you rich bitch?
Huh?
All right, that's enough.
I forbid you to lay
another finger on Madam.
Madam, you should try learning a
bit more about Japanese culture.
Okay.
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't tell her Miss Holly
only has a few days left.
It would break her heart.
And that's the last thing
I would ever want to do.
We've almost arrived, and
I still haven't told her.
I can't put this off any longer.
We'll soon be in sight of the Kujo house.
She needs to hear this from me.
It's okay.
I know there's something
you want to tell me.
You don't need to pretend anymore.
I'm well aware of what's
troubling you, Roses.
My daughter's life is in
grave danger, isn't it?
I called Holly from New York a few times.
She put on a brave face and
pretended to be cheerful and lively.
She tried her best to convince
me it was only a mild cold.
Whenever Joseph phoned,
he would tell me his business
trip kept him very busy,
but that I had nothing to worry about.
But I knew they were keeping
something important from me.
Deep down, I knew something terrible was
happening to my daughter and husband.
I've been married to
Joseph for 50 years now,
and my sweet Holly is
my own flesh and blood.
I never pressed them for more information
because I was afraid of what they'd say.
I wanted nothing more than
to see my precious daughter.
But the thought of what I'd
find here was almost too much!
You know this much, so you also
have the right to know the rest.
As it stands, your daughter only
has a few days left to live.
That's why Mr.
Joestar and the others went to Egypt
To end the source of her illness?
But there's been no news for a while.
Please, can you find it in your heart
to forgive me for not telling you?
There was nothing we could do for Miss Holly
so I wanted to spare you from the pain,
but I was wrong.
I should have told you.
It was cruel of me not to.
I don't want to hear any more
of that foolishness, Roses.
No matter how grim things seem, there's
still one thing we can do for Holly.
Hi, sweet girl.
I'm so glad you're here.
Listen to me very carefully, Roses.
Right now, the one thing we can
do for my daughter is have faith.
I don't understand everything that's
happening, but here's what I do know.
Joseph and my grandson, Jotaro,
are putting their lives on the
line in the hope of saving Holly.
And I believe they will
find a way to do just that.
He's never failed me.
Not once in the 50 years I have known him.
He's kept every promise he's made
since the two of us met in Italy.
Once he's made up his mind to do something,
nothing in this world can stop him.
Rest and believe in
Jotaro and your father.
You'll be better before you know it, and
our family will be together once again.
Thank you, Mama.
Madam Joestar, Miss Holly,
please hang in there.
That cool ice, Billy
Jean, even Darby Younger.
I knew they were nothing
but incompetent fools.
I shouldn't laugh, but knowing they got
what they deserve feels so satisfying.
That's what the fools get
for calling me a loser.
But at least now we know
I wasn't one after all!
Don't be absurd.
You can't possibly defeat the
Joestars using that pathetic power.
Out of the way, loser.
Hey, but that's not fair!
I want a chance to fight them too!
You're merely an ordinary vampire.
You'd best stay out of our way
or we might end up killing you!
Do try to behave yourself, loser.
I'll be the one who finishes off Jotaro!
Stop!
There's something up ahead, to the right!
A woman.
Please have mercy on me!
I'm begging you!
Don't suck my blood!
Anything but that!
I swear I'll do whatever you want.
Just let me live.
That's all I'm asking.
Hey, easy now.
You need to calm down.
I won't run away anymore.
You can trust me.
Please have mercy.
Just breathe.
We aren't Dio's minions, and
we're certainly not vampires.
We're the good guys.
So just calm down and let us help you.
You're good guys?
Good guys?
You're really not those evil vampires?
You're actually going to
help me get away from here?
That's right. We're good.
Real good at punching evil in the face.
If you still want help,
we'll be happy to oblige.
We'll help by sending you
on a one-way trip to hell.
Sound good, Kakyoin?
Help!
Damn it! Help! Tell me! Help! Help!
How did you figure it out?
My power is impossible to crack!
Would this power have anything to do with
the face of a woman on
the back of your head?
For future reference,
when you flip your head,
you should make sure your hands match too.
Shit! You're right!
I never noticed!
I'm an idiot!
No, you're a loser.
Now where is Dio's room? Out with it.
Jotaro, try not to knock him unconscious.
He can take us to Dio.
How dare you!
Don't you call me that!
You're just like those other guys,
so you'll meet the same fate!
I'll kill you!
Lord Dio's powers made me immortal!
And I'll use all of it
to rip you to pieces!
So unless I heard wrong, you
just said you were an immortal.
So you're a vampire like Dio.
In which case,
I can use you as a practice dummy for
when I fight against the real thing.
Oh my god!
So you really are immortal.
Vampire or not,
we can still rip you into little pieces
and scatter them around the room.
Well, are you taking us to Dio or not?
The sun is about to set.
Okay, but can I at
least ask you one thing?
How the hell did you know the other
stand users used to call me loser?
Oh man, good grief.
Thank you.
I gotta hand it to him.
Dio's got some pretty nice curtains.
All right.
Now I can walk and even
jump around if I need to.
It still hurts a bit, but now's not
the time to worry about a little pain.
Greetings, Polareff.
What a pleasant surprise.
Dio, at last.
You've finally come out, Dio.
I knew this day would come.
I have absolutely no regrets.
There's something you need to hear first.
Is he playing games with us?
When did he bring out his stand?
I'll give you a chance to rethink.